Lloyd: Now that you've completed session
two it's time to compete the relevant
section in the assessment booklet.
So if you haven't already done so you
can download the assessment booklet by
clicking on the assessment link on page
three of session two, and saving that
in a suitable location on the computer.
Once you've done that, you can then
open the assessment booklet and scroll
down to section two, which is about
understanding the need for cyber security.
At the top of section two, you'll
see the learning outcomes and also
which question it is and where the
information relating to that is
located in the course materials.
So for question one, in the table
below list common cyber crime
vulnerabilities of the following: an
individual, a business and a nation.
Just before we look at that, if you
look at question two and question
three, they all relate to an
individual, a business and a nation.
So question one is about
the vulnerabilities.
Question two is about
the potential impact.
And question three is about the
importance of cybersecurity for
individuals, businesses and a nation.
So what you need to do is you need to
think about that but when we're talking
about a business, you can see that it's
been emphasised there being bold, but
you need to think about the potential
impact on charities, multi-organisationals
for an example, would be the NHS
and international organisations.
Why, what is the potential
impact on those organisations?
Why is a charity at high risk?
Why are mutli-organisationals
at high risk?
Why are international
organisations at high risk and
what is the potential impact?
So why are they vulnerable?
Potential impact.
And why is cyber security
important for those organisations?
For question four, it's asking
you to explain why cyber security
issues should be reported promptly.
So why should you report these
incidents, if one occurs, promptly?
What's the benefits of doing that?
What are the consequences of
not reporting it promptly?
And once you've done that, you
can then move on to section three.